let hardmultiplicationquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 16 x 19",
        AnswerA: "302",
        AnswerB: "304",
        AnswerC: "306",
        AnswerD: "308",
        correctAnswer: "304",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 x 30",
        AnswerA: "260",
        AnswerB: "270",
        AnswerC: "280",
        AnswerD: "290",
        correctAnswer: "270",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 25",
        AnswerA: "165",
        AnswerB: "170",
        AnswerC: "175",
        AnswerD: "180",
        correctAnswer: "175",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 8 x 22",
        AnswerA: "173",
        AnswerB: "174",
        AnswerC: "175",
        AnswerD: "176",
        correctAnswer: "176",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 34 x 7",
        AnswerA: "234",
        AnswerB: "236",
        AnswerC: "237",
        AnswerD: "238",
        correctAnswer: "238",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 29 x 8",
        AnswerA: "229",
        AnswerB: "231",
        AnswerC: "232",
        AnswerD: "233",
        correctAnswer: "232",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 x 8",
        AnswerA: "191",
        AnswerB: "192",
        AnswerC: "193",
        AnswerD: "194",
        correctAnswer: "192",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 x 12",
        AnswerA: "202",
        AnswerB: "203",
        AnswerC: "204",
        AnswerD: "205",
        correctAnswer: "204",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 x 14",
        AnswerA: "264",
        AnswerB: "266",
        AnswerC: "267",
        AnswerD: "268",
        correctAnswer: "266",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 44 x 9",
        AnswerA: "392",
        AnswerB: "394",
        AnswerC: "396",
        AnswerD: "398",
        correctAnswer: "396",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 33 x 8",
        AnswerA: "262",
        AnswerB: "264",
        AnswerC: "266",
        AnswerD: "268",
        correctAnswer: "264",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 + 6",
        AnswerA: "282",
        AnswerB: "284",
        AnswerC: "286",
        AnswerD: "288",
        correctAnswer: "288",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 x 12",
        AnswerA: "311",
        AnswerB: "312",
        AnswerC: "313",
        AnswerD: "314",
        correctAnswer: "312",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 x 11",
        AnswerA: "192",
        AnswerB: "194",
        AnswerC: "196",
        AnswerD: "198",
        correctAnswer: "198",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 x 12",
        AnswerA: "225",
        AnswerB: "226",
        AnswerC: "227",
        AnswerD: "228",
        correctAnswer: "228",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 72",
        AnswerA: "502",
        AnswerB: "504",
        AnswerC: "506",
        AnswerD: "508",
        correctAnswer: "504",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 78 x 9",
        AnswerA: "702",
        AnswerB: "704",
        AnswerC: "706",
        AnswerD: "708",
        correctAnswer: "702",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 x 9",
        AnswerA: "422",
        AnswerB: "423",
        AnswerC: "424",
        AnswerD: "425",
        correctAnswer: "423",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 14 x 18",
        AnswerA: "252",
        AnswerB: "253",
        AnswerC: "254",
        AnswerD: "255",
        correctAnswer: "252",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 x 17",
        AnswerA: "321",
        AnswerB: "322",
        AnswerC: "323",
        AnswerD: "324",
        correctAnswer: "323",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 x 20",
        AnswerA: "290",
        AnswerB: "300",
        AnswerC: "305",
        AnswerD: "310",
        correctAnswer: "300",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 54 x 9",
        AnswerA: "482",
        AnswerB: "483",
        AnswerC: "484",
        AnswerD: "486",
        correctAnswer: "486",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 81 x 9",
        AnswerA: "726",
        AnswerB: "727",
        AnswerC: "729",
        AnswerD: "731",
        correctAnswer: "729",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 62 x 6",
        AnswerA: "672",
        AnswerB: "673",
        AnswerC: "674",
        AnswerD: "676",
        correctAnswer: "672",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 x 4",
        AnswerA: "195",
        AnswerB: "196",
        AnswerC: "197",
        AnswerD: "198",
        correctAnswer: "196",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 x 8",
        AnswerA: "275",
        AnswerB: "280",
        AnswerC: "285",
        AnswerD: "290",
        correctAnswer: "280",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 67 x 7",
        AnswerA: "466",
        AnswerB: "467",
        AnswerC: "468",
        AnswerD: "469",
        correctAnswer: "469",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 x 9",
        AnswerA: "231",
        AnswerB: "232",
        AnswerC: "233",
        AnswerD: "234",
        correctAnswer: "234",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 x 11",
        AnswerA: "261",
        AnswerB: "262",
        AnswerC: "263",
        AnswerD: "264",
        correctAnswer: "264",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 x 12",
        AnswerA: "322",
        AnswerB: "324",
        AnswerC: "326",
        AnswerD: "328",
        correctAnswer: "324",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 36 x 16",
        AnswerA: "572",
        AnswerB: "574",
        AnswerC: "576",
        AnswerD: "578",
        correctAnswer: "576",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 x 12",
        AnswerA: "308",
        AnswerB: "312",
        AnswerC: "314",
        AnswerD: "316",
        correctAnswer: "312",
    },
]